filetypeadvisor.com 2017-07-30

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction

This document discloses what information we collect from visitors of our site and users of our software, and how the collected information is used. We respect your privacy.

Please read this document carefully to understand our Privacy Policy. Using our products or services signifies accepting this Privacy Policy.

### What Information We Collect

We use no cookies or other identifiers to track visitors of www.filetypeadvisor.com . As you visit our site, we may collect information about your system, such as IP address, operating system and its version, screen resolution, browser type, system language. This information cannot be used to identify you personally.

The File Type Advisor software program, when installed on your computer, will send the following information to our server: name and frequency of the CPU installed on your computer, version of your operating system, version of File Type Advisor, its interface language, an anonymous identifier of your computer, information about installed or running software that includes the name of the product, its version, publisher, home page, download page, associated file types and their descriptions.

If you use our contact form, you may be asked to supply your name and email address.

### How We Use The Collected Information

Information about installed software is used for the purpose of showing you update prompts when new versions of the software installed on your computer are made available by the corresponding publishers. Furthermore, information about registered file types may be used to improve our services.

Information about your system is used for the purpose of anonymous statistics.

Any information you provide about yourself on our contact form is used solely for the purpose of contacting you and replying to your request. We do not send spam.

### Sharing The Collected Information

As described above, most information we collect is anonymous (screen resolution, operating system version, etc.) or publicly available (publisher, home page, download page of a particular software program). We do not share any information we receive about yourself or your system with any person or organization. We do not share your name, email address or other information provided by you on our contact form.

### Changes

We reserve the right to review, update or change this Privacy Policy. The latest revision of the Privacy Policy can always be found in the "Privacy Policy" section of our site. The page you are reading contains the latest revision of our Privacy Policy.
